Joseph Hancock

1700 Burton Dr Austin, TX 78741

832-455-2639 - joe.hancock95@gmail.com

Profile

Very diligent and hard working. Published author and responsible worker very interested in new opportunities and positions in order to further grow my knowledge of customer service and gain new experiences. Responsible, easy to work with, and open to learning new things.

Education

- Completed 4 years at Seven Lakes High School (2009-2013), Graduated June 2013 with a 3.2 GPA
- Completed 2 years at Austin Community College and 2 years at Texas State University towards a BA in history
- Currently enrolled in Full stack web development program at UT Austin.

Work Experience

Republic of Sandwich

(May 2015 to February 2017)

- Provided knowledgeable and factual information about products we sold and the process of making them.
- Listened to customers preferences to ensure satisfactory experience and give them the best options on our menu
- Greeted and talked with every customer to make sure they were served a quality meal they would recommend to others.

Electric Church

(February 2017 to 2018)

- Quick and courteous bartender
- Responsible for stocking inventory, scheduling, and payroll among other day to day tasks such as bartender
 or doorman.
- Good communication skills in order to manage day to day operations and also book different bands and acts

Conscious Cravings

(December 2018 to present)

- Reliable and quick line cook
- Prompt customer service and food output without sacrificing quality. Able to work by myself even on busy days, handling multiple positions simultaneously.
- Quick thinking in high pressure situations
- Responsible inventory management skills. Making sure to order correct ingredients on time.

Skills and Abilities

- Take pride in ensuring the job is done right and done well
- Know how to learn several POS and a quick learner to new technology
- Strong writer and communicator allowing me to be a good team member or solo worker
- Very punctual and good at managing my time. Making sure when the store is slow that other tasks are tended too
- Able to manage several tasks at once and handle pressure well.